In this video, I will introduce you to some of the areas becomes which are pretty useful when you work
with them.
Terminal window.
So here are some of the common areas commands.
So the first one here is to get top command.
So this basically brings the top air speak directly.
Let's quickly try this in the terminal window.
I'm now in the device common folder type.
Get your print start up a hospital folder right from this particular part.
So I'm now in device common, right if I need to go directly to another folder.
Go to framework base.
So I could simply use CD.
Get Doc so the top will print you.
The top four part like Mount Lennox is spit on and from there you put a slash and framework based.
So it's a good.
This command then checked out, but then you are already in the framework base.
So this is a typical use case where you could make use of this get document.
So simply typing their talk will bring you top air speed dual folder.
So similarly, if you want to go back to the device comment, then what you could do is just give your
device.
Slash government, you are already in the device government.
So now let's look at the federal government change rules so you can change the folder directly with
the root areas, be bolder.
So let's see this in action.
OK, just let's clear this off.
So if you simply type just took the part.
So currently you are in Dubai common.
You simply type C rule.
Then you will be back in the hospital for that, so matter where you are from there.
You simply type through change route, so then it will change directly to the root areas, people.
Or maybe another quick example like just go inside, build a blueprint, maybe from here.
So now you are in A.P. Tool Build Blueprint, and from here, if you just simply type C, Root will
be back in the hospital for that.
So the next command is employment will basically build.
The package will build the package within the current folder.
Now I'm in the air hospital folder, so from here I would like to go to one of each.
So I have selected packages, apps, dialer package for sure.
There's no an app from this app quickly modify or just open things the time stamp of the manifest or
eczema.
OK, let's see.
So from here, if I simply type M, then it will build or lead the dialer.
We could see here it's actually building or later dialler intermediate classes.
And so it's generating the facts.
Plus us and our tax files.
OK, so it's generating the epic.
So it's done.
So then you can see that it's it's actually generated here that I love, not Epic Games here.
And if you want to directly install this epic, you could simply copy this and ADB it, see if there's
any device available.
You install base that part, so it'll install the emulator.
Then we have the grep commands.
So we have C grep, J grep and Harrison up.
So single piece only four matching C C++ files.
Zagreb is only for Java source files and Russell Group is only for the source files.
So let's try the C Group First C grep.
Let's search for network.
So here you can see it searching all the C C++ files.
And so these are the header files and it's showing where over the network keyword is used.
Similarly, let's try the J grep.
Take it up.
Let's search for network again.
So these are all our clients, as you can see here.
And now let's try a resource reverse grep network and see.
Here you go.
So there are places where network exists, so it is only showing the small files, as you can see here,
see.
OK, so see grip and grip and grip.
So these are also critical, convenient if you want to search from the window.
OK, then another one is to go directly.
OK, so this command will help you to go to a particular directly rail where one particular file exists.
So go directly.
Let's go to the system server, fold up.
So then I need to search for the Sims outdoor tower.
OK, it's not found, so I think I need to add.
Yeah.
No.
OK, so now it was successful, and if you check you are already inside the folder where the system,
Sahwa or Java exist.
And from here, if you want to jump to the system UI you or Java, then you are already in system.
You are.